https://www.subaru.net/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to subaru.net. We want you to feel comfortable when you access our website. When you visit this site, you can do so anonymously without revealing your identity or any personal information to us.
We also believe that understanding what our customers want to see and do when visiting our site is an important part of building an interesting and useful online environment. Therefore, we track, on an aggregate basis, such information as the time and length of visits, the pages viewed or downloaded and your browser version. We do not collect any personal information about you unless you provide it to us.
Information Gathered
When you request a brochure, request a quote, opt-in for updates or send an e-mail message to us, you voluntarily give us personal information such as your name, address and e-mail address. If you choose to share this information with us, it is stored in our database so that we can respond to you and fulfill your requests for information. Please be assured that this information is stored in a responsible and secure manner to protect your privacy. The information gathered by us when you request a brochure or quote, send an e-mail message, or opt-in for updates may be used for Subaru-affiliated marketing purposes. None of this information is ever sold to marketers, periodical publishers or any other outsiders. We use this information only within the Subaru family.
If you previously gave us your email address and no longer wish to receive email announcements, you can have your name removed from our email list by contacting us.
Cookies
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. subaru.net uses two kinds of cookies – session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary cookies that last on your computer only as long as you are on the subaru.net web site, and expire when you leave the site or when you close your browser. If your browser is set to block temporary cookies, it is possible some parts of the site may not function properly. subaru.net uses a persistent 3rd party cookie to help us identify the areas of our site that are most important to our customers which, in turn, helps ensure you will have a pleasant visit when you come to subaru.net. If your browser or security software blocks persistent cookies and/or 3rd party cookies this should not affect site use in any way.
Summary
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we gather from this site to enhance your overall experience, and we will not sell your personal information to anyone. If we can answer any questions or concerns you may have about our privacy policy, please contact us and we’ll be happy to help in any way we can.
News Categories
Subaru News
Newsreel
Features
CPD Racing
Featured Videos
News
Subaru News
©2020 Subenet, LLC • Call Toll Free: (800) 332-4266 or Direct: (952) 797-1319
This site powered by Scott Putnam
